现在，您需要的一件事
Now, one of the things that you need
为了完成这门课程
in order to go through this course is
访问一些启动文件
to get access to some starter files
对于本课程的每个部分。
for each of the sections in this course.
所以在这个视频中，
And so in this video,
让我很快告诉你
let me very quickly show you
如何访问这些文件。
how you can access those files.
所以整个启动文件，
So the entire starter files,
以及每个人的最终文件
as well as the final files for each
课程的部分
of the sections of the course
托管在 GitHub 上的这个所谓的存储库中。
are hosted in this so-called repository on GitHub.
而GitHub基本上是一个代码平台
And GitHub is basically a code platform
大多数开发人员将他们的代码上传到的地方，
where most developers upload their code to,
为了分享或合作
in order to share it or to collaborate
与其他开发人员或只是存储它。
with other developers or simply to store it.
所以存储库基本上是一个文件夹
So a repository is basically a folder
其中包含一堆代码或其他文件。
which contains a bunch of code or other files.
每个存储库都可以通过 URL 访问
And each repository can be accessed by a URL
并且此存储库在此可用，URL 在这里。
and this repository is available on this, URL here.
但别担心，你不必输入它。
But don't worry, you don't have to type that in.
所以我在这个关于 Udemy 的讲座中加入了这个链接，
So I included this link in this lecture on Udemy,
它也应该在第一次课文中
and it should also be in the very first text lecture
本节的。
of this section.
所以我相信你可以在这里找到这个链接，
So I'm sure that you can find this link here,
所以这个 URL，在这个讲座的某个地方。
so this URL, somewhere in this lecture.
所以只需点击它，然后你就会结束
So just click that and then you will end up
在这个完全相同的存储库上。
on this exact same repository.
所以在这个存储库中，正如我提到的，
So in this repository, as I mentioned,
我们有所有的启动文件
we have all the starter files
对于课程的每个部分，
and for each of the sections of the course,
有1个文件夹。
there is 1 folder.
例如，下一节，
For example, the next section,
这是 HTML 基础知识，
which are the HTML Fundamentals,
包含所有这些图像以及此文本文档。
contains all of these images and also this text document.
好的，我还包含了最终代码
Okay, I also included the final code
对于每个部分，
for each of the sections,
这样您就可以随时比较自己的代码
so that you can always compare your own code
到我在视频中编写的代码。
to the code that I'm writing in the videos.
这将是非常重要的，
And this will be very important,
这样您就可以将您的代码与我的代码进行比较
so that you can compare your code to mine
以防您的代码有任何错误。
in case that you have any mistakes in your code.
因此，将您的代码与我的代码进行比较，就像这样，
So comparing your code to mine, like this,
将永远是您发现错误的最简单方法，
will always be your easiest way of finding mistakes,
所以发现你可能在你的代码中输入的错误
so of finding errors that you are maybe typing in your code
这肯定会发生。
and that will happen for sure.
它发生在所有初学者身上。
It happens to all beginners.
所以在那种情况下，
And so in that situation,
您可以访问最终代码。
you can just get access to the final code.
最后，在下面，还有这个书面文件，
Finally, down here, there is also this written document,
其中包含这些最常见的问题。
which contains these most frequently asked questions.
所以在真正开始课程之前，
So before actually starting the course,
快速阅读可能是个好主意
it might be a good idea to quickly read
通过这些问题。
through these questions.
这应该只需要你大约 3 分钟，
That should only take you like 3 minutes,
但我相信它会帮助你消除一些疑虑
but I'm sure it will help you clear some doubts
您在完成课程时可能会得到。
that you might get as you go through the course.
但无论如何，我们真正来到这里的目的
But anyway, what we really came here to
是实际访问代码，对吗？
is to actually get access to the code, right?
所以要下载这个代码，
And so to download this code,
我们所要做的就是点击这个绿色按钮
all we have to do is to click here on this green button
然后在此处选择下载 zip 选项。
and then down here choosing the download zip option.
现在这可能需要一些时间
And now this should probably take some time
因为这里有很多图片。
because there are a lot of images here.
所以让我们等待这个下载完成。
And so let's just wait for this download to finish.
好的，下载刚刚完成。
Okay, and that download just finished.
现在让我们回到桌面
Now let's go back to the desktop
或者你在哪里工作。
or wherever you are working.
和T让我们简单地说
And then let's simply put
我们刚刚下载的那些文件。
those files that we just downloaded there.
好的，那么我们需要解压这个 zip 存档
All right, so then we need to extract this zip archive
在 Mac 上，
and on a Mac,
您只需双击该文件
you just have to double click that file
在 Windows 上，
and on Windows,
您只需右键单击然后提取所有内容。
you just right click and then extract all.
好的，所以我们不再需要它了。
Okay, so we don't need that anymore.
现在让我们快速打开这个文件夹，
And now let's quickly open up this folder,
这样我们就可以看到它确实是
just so we can see that it is indeed
我们刚刚在 GitHub 上看到的完全相同的文件。
the exact same files that we just saw on GitHub.
所以我们有启动文件
So we have the starter files
在这里，下一节的文件，
and here, the files for the next section,
然后还有最终文件。
and then also the final files.
所以现在有了这些启动文件，
And so now with these starter files in place,
我们实际上已经准备好开始学习 HTML
we are actually ready to start learning HTML
在下一节中。
in the next section.